翻译  妖精希亚
翻译  国士章鱼X
翻译  ET外星人
翻译  杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译  沫沫
翻译  丶Charl
翻译  痒痒惦记小跟班
时间轴  ans
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
第四季  第九集
纸牌屋
人人影视倾情奉献
民主党全国代表大会
副总统提名点名投票
斯考特·希尔参议员
肯塔基州  民主党
民主党全国代表大会  亚特兰大
总统接见器官捐赠者家属
安东尼·莫雷蒂基金
安东尼·莫雷蒂纪念基金
捐赠
康威和布洛哈特在亚特兰大
名利场
康威夫妇
谁是第一夫人  克莱尔·安德伍德还是凯瑟琳·杜兰特
第三轮投票即将开始
第一夫人成副总统候选人有力竞争者
第二轮投票结果
杜兰特
安德伍德
肯塔基  你们有53票
Kentucky, you have 53 votes.
你们要投给谁
How do you cast them?
秘书长女士
Madam Secretary,
作为肯塔基州参议员
as a senator for the great Commonwealth of Kentucky,
我很荣幸以代表团的名义发言
I'm proud to speak on behalf of the delegation's chair.
肯塔基联邦
The Commonwealth of Kentucky,
德比赛马会之乡  野猫队之乡
home of the Derby, the Wildcats,
波本酒的发源地
and the birthplace of bourbon,
在美国副总统提名投票上
for Vice President of the United States,
将13票投给国务卿凯瑟琳·杜兰特
casts 13 votes for Secretary of State Catherine Durant...
11票投给内华达州参议员约瑟夫·贝克
11 for Senator Joseph Baker of Nevada,
9票投给西弗吉尼亚州州长兰道尔·史密斯
9 for Governor Randall Smith of West Virginia,
佛罗里达州州长吉尔·哈利
7 apiece for Governor Jill Haley of Florida
和加州议员莎伦·皮尔斯女士各7票
and Congresswoman Sharon Pierce of California,
5票投给我们路易斯维尔市长  吉尔·卡森
5 for one of our own, the Mayor of Louisville, Jill Carson...
还有1票投给美国第一夫人
and 1 vote for the First Lady of these United States,
克莱尔·安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Claire Underwood.
路易斯安那  你们共有61票
Louisiana, you have 61 votes.
你们都投给谁
How do you cast them?
很激动人心吧  可以感受到热烈的气氛
Isn't this exciting? You can feel the electricity.
好久没举办过开放党代会了
Been a very long time since an open convention.
我很意外您自己一票都没有  参议员
I'm surprised you didn't get a few votes yourself, Senator.
我没参选副总统
I'm not running for vice president.
克莱尔·安德伍德也没有  她还是得了一票
Neither is Claire Underwood and she got one.
是我投的
That was my vote.
是想增加点趣味吗  先生
Trying to throw some levity into the proceedings, sir?
才不是  我认为她能胜任副总统
Hell, no! I think she'd make a terrific vice president.
安德伍德夫人  安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood! Mrs. Underwood!
我有几个问题  安德伍德夫人  您有时间吗
A couple of questions, Mrs. Underwood, if you have a moment?
可以  我只有几分钟
Yes, I only have time for a few.
欢迎来到亚特兰大  安德伍德夫人
Welcome to Atlanta, Mrs. Underwood.
谢谢
Thank you.
您能对希尔参议员的投票发表评论吗
Can you comment on Senator Sheer's vote?
我很荣幸  但我相信他是开玩笑的
Well, I am flattered. But it's all in good fun, I'm sure.
安德伍德夫人  他说他还会再为您投票
Mrs. Underwood, he says he'll vote for you again.
我鼓励所有人  包括希尔参议员
Well, I am encouraging everyone, including Senator Sheer,
把票投给凯茜·杜兰特
to vote for Cathy Durant.
总统和我
Both the president and I
都认为她是这个职位的最佳人选
think she is the best choice in the field.
你把我们写的稿全改了
You changed everything we wrote.
那个稿子没有创意  也不押韵
There was no imagination to it. No rhythm.
从他们就职就是我们在为他们写讲稿
We've been writing their speeches since they took office.
我们知道自己在做什么
We know what we're doing.
你们在意的是好讲稿  还是撰稿人署名
Well, do you want it to be good, or do you want it to be yours?
最让我激动的投票
The vote I'm most excited about
是昨天在众议院
is the victory our
我们的《背景普查法案》取得的胜利
Background Check Legislation got in the House yesterday.
所以我希望参议院也能尽快向他们学习
So I'm hoping that the Senate will follow their lead soon,
这样总统就能签署这一法案
and that the president can sign it into law.
我得走了  非常感谢
I have to go. Thank you so much.
谢谢您邀请我们
Thank you... for inviting us.
不
No.
是我应该谢谢你和你儿子
It's me who has to thank you and your son.
他救了我的命
He saved my life.
虽然是因为那样一场悲剧
No matter how tragic the circumstances.
我想带你见见其他接受者
I want you to meet some of the other recipients.
这是詹姆斯
This is James...
他接受了你儿子的一个肾
who received one of your son's kidneys.
这是路易莎
And this is Luisa...
她接受了你儿子的心脏
who received your son's heart.
路易莎是名单上的第一个
Luisa was at the top of the list.
她本就剩几小时的生命了
She was hours away from dying.
如果可以的话  我们一起拍个照吧
Uh, if we could, let's all get together for a photo.
詹姆斯  过来
James? Right here.
-你到这儿来  -好的
- You come right here. - Okay.
好了
All right.
这边  很好
This way. Great.
总统对他的移植手术并不避讳
The president isn't shying away from, uh, his transplant.
我认为这是明智之举
Well, I think it's a smart move.
既然不能否认  何必要隐瞒呢
You can't deny it, so why try to hide it?
另外  我认为这也强调了
Plus, I think it underscores the importance
副总统选举的重要性
of the vice presidential situation.
等等  把捐赠者的妈妈拉出来  感觉像在作秀
Wait, rolling out the donor's mom? That feels a bit exploitative.
我...等等
I... Look, hold on.
有点同情心  那孩子刚刚饮弹自尽了
A little bit of compassion, the kid just shot himself.
而且是用一把手枪
And with a handgun, no less.
合法购买的  不要把重点转移到枪上
Legally purchased. Let's not put this on the gun.
很抱歉  这一切
Look, I am sorry, all of this, the whole thing,
党代会...都是制造戏剧效果
the convention... It's theatrics.
闹起来吧
Hey, look, I... bring on the circus.
比四天的专题广告片有趣多了
It's a lot more fun than some four-day infomercial.
我们来说说竞选者吧
Let's talk about the contenders themselves.
足有十多个
There's almost a dozen of 'em.
-你能小点声吗  -...确实有机会的
- Can you, uh, lower that, please? - ...really have a chance.
杜兰特是头一个
Durant, first among 'em.
这才第一天  上午11点
It's 11:00 in the morning, day one,
收视率比《艾伦秀》还高
and they're beating Ellen.
网站的流量也少了
Less traffic on the website, too.
看视频的人越来越少了
People aren't watching the videos as much.
这个卖了一百多万份
This sold over a million copies.
是网上阅读量的五倍
Five times that many read it online.
对  那是上个月  这是这个月
Yeah, well, that was last month. This is this month.
我们公开了一位重量级竞选搭档
We announce a stellar running mate.
他在哈里发国问题上重创了安德伍德
He eviscerates Underwood on ICO.
我们手里有两个
We have not one, but two
《名利场》封面供波利跳推送
Vanity Fair covers that Pollyhop's pushing,
而你们却在这里大找借口
and all you give me is excuses.
应该是我们的曝光率压制他们的党代会
The point was for us to drown out their convention,
而不是反过来  我们得把风头夺回来
not the other way around. We need to steal the thunder back.
那就去风口夺风头
So go where the thunder is.
两年来  我一直近在咫尺
I've been one heartbeat away for almost two years.
我对这个已经没兴趣了
My heart's not in it anymore.
过了11月我就回佛蒙特去了
I'm going to head back to Vermont after November.
也许继续教书
Maybe start teaching again.
那你支持谁呢
Who are you supporting, then?
公开说是凯茜·杜兰特
On the record, Cathy Durant.
私下里呢
And off the record?
我不是很喜欢她
I'm not the biggest fan.
为什么
Why?
俄罗斯危机期间她没帮上什么忙
She wasn't much help during the Russia crisis.
可是她和佩特罗夫达成了协议
She closed the deal with Petrov.
功劳的确是归到她头上了
She took credit for it, sure.
但她从始至终都在阻挠那份协议
But she fought the deal every step of the way.
如果不是克莱尔  根本就不可能成
Nothing would've happened if it weren't for Claire.
第一夫人
The First Lady?
是前大使
The former ambassador.
我们在堪萨斯的支持率更接近了  但还不够
We're closer in Kansas, but still not close enough.
你去争取众议院票时
Did you speak to Jefferies
和杰弗瑞斯谈过了吗
when you were there for the House vote?
他正在向弗雷德·西姆斯施压
He's leaning on Fred Simms.
如果西姆斯可以拉来两三名代表
If Simms could deliver two or three delegates--
那就能拿下整个堪萨斯了
That could push Kansas over the edge.
我可以联系乌麦克
I can call Womack.
他在那边有几个朋友
He's got some friends over the border.
-珀利怎么样  -珀利
- What about Pawley? - Pawley?
沃思堡治安官珀利  是我爸的老朋友了
Sheriff Pawley in Fort Worth, old family friend of my dad's.
他和达拉斯的几位超级代表关系很近
He's close with some superdelegates from Dallas.
可以拉他过来
Yes, he's on board.
真得喜欢那些治安官
Gotta love those sheriffs.
我们在路易斯安那就是那么做的
That's how we do in Louisiana.
恩莱特呢
What about Enright?
我和他约好了在凯悦喝咖啡
I'm meeting him for coffee at the Hyatt.
话说我该过去了  我可不想迟到
In fact, I better get going. I don't wanna be late.
如果我们能拿下弗吉尼亚
Now, if we could lock up Virginia--
就会向全国发出强势的讯息
It would send a very big message.
接下来就是肯塔基
And then Kentucky next.
肯塔基可喜欢你了
He's got a big old crush on you.
那你最好赶紧上路
We better get you on a move.
恩莱特最讨厌不守时了
Enright is a stickler for punctuality.
我挺开心的  我都忘了我多喜欢做党鞭
You know, I'm having fun. I forgot how much I miss being whip.
鞭子你来抽  蜜糖我来喂
You whip 'em. I'll sweet talk 'em.
胡萝卜加大棒最有效了
Nothing like leather and sugar.
先生
Sir?
希尔参议员
Senator Sheer.
参议员  你干得太漂亮了
Senator, you did a fine job.
我最好能拿到黄金时段
Yeah, I better get prime time,
而不是在垃圾时段发表讲话
not one of these midmorning speeches.
周三晚上八点  我亲自和帕特打招呼
Eight o'clock, Wednesday night. I called Patti myself.
你知道政客这个物种
Do you know the main thing that separates
和其他物种最大的区别是什么吗
a politician from the rest of the species?
政客愿意淹死一窝小猫
A politician is the one who would drown a litter of kittens
来换十分钟的黄金时段
for ten minutes of prime time.
杜兰特国务卿  我是政治新闻网的总编
Secretary Durant. Editor in chief, Politico.
没事的
It's all right.
亚当  你亲自来做报道吗
Adam, are you covering this yourself?
68年以来的第一次开放党代会
First open one since '68.
不过这天够潮的
It's humid as hell, though.
我刚来就浑身透湿了
I just got here and I'm already soaked.
不过往好处想
On the plus side,
我听说这里的艳舞俱乐部全国顶尖
I hear they have the best strip clubs in the country.
我能问几个问题吗
Can I ask you a couple questions?
-我有点急事  -就几个
- Well, I'm in a hurry. - Just a couple.
不能公开
Nothing on the record.
和我说说关于
Tell me about the rumors
你在勃兰登堡和佩特罗夫谈判的传闻吧
regarding the deal you struck with Petrov in Brandenburg.
什么传闻
What rumors?
是第一夫人谈妥的协议  而不是你
That it was the First Lady who brokered the deal, not you.
那是团队合作的成果  是谁告诉你的
It was a team effort. Who is your source?
我不能透露  你懂的
I can't. You know that.
实在抱歉  我没有时间了
Well, I'm afraid that's all the time I've got.
行程顺利  亚当
Have a good trip, Adam.
总统今早和凯伦·威廉姆斯一起
The president was on site this morning for a press briefing
在特斯顿侯爵酒店召开了记者会
at the Truxton Marquis with Karen Williams,
凯伦的儿子丹尼尔·威廉姆斯
the mother of Daniel Williams,
是他所用肝脏的捐献者
the organ donor who provided his liver.
一起出席的还有其他器官接受者
Alongside him were all of the donor organs' recipients.
威廉姆斯太太和每一位接受者进行了交谈
Ms. Williams took time to speak with each recipient
是她已逝儿子的器官挽救了他们的生命
whose life was saved in the wake of her son's passing.
总统借此肃穆的场合
The president used this solemn event
表达了他对分享生命拯救他人健康
to express his gratitude for those who share their lives
和幸福的人的敬意
for the health and welfare of others,
无论是通过捐赠器官  还是工作
whether through organ donation or through their work.
总统在接受器官移植后
The president's condition has improved dramatically
健康状况大为好转
since his organ donation.
他住院期间
The entire country was on edge
全国人民的心都悬在空中
throughout his time in the hospital.
16岁少年丹尼尔
Sixteen-year-old Daniel,
把安德伍德总统从健康危机中解救了出来
who saved President Underwood from his health crisis,
他离开了这个世界
left this world by
却回馈了很多他并不知道自己会触动的人
giving back to so many others he never expected to touch.
这样永恒的礼物是不会被遗忘的
Lasting tributes like this will not be forgotten.
目前  每年都有超过12.2万的男人
Currently, there are more than 122,000 men,
女人和小孩
women and children
在寻求器官移植
seeking an organ transplant each year,
最常见的需求是肾脏  肝脏和心脏
most common needs being the kidney, liver, and heart.
虽然这些年来  捐赠者的数量有所上升
And while the number of donors has increased over the years,
接受者在找到一个健康匹配的器官前
recipients are still in for a long, potentially fatal waiting period
仍要熬过一段漫长且可能致命的等待期
before a healthy, matching organ becomes available.
这类移植的等待者
Waiting lists for these types of transplants
能坚持从几天到几个月不等
can last from days to months on end.
虽然安德伍德总统因情况紧急
Although President Underwood's critical condition
而登上了捐赠名单榜首
pushed him to the top of the donor list,
但他能及时获得捐赠仍然是很幸运的
he was fortunate to have received a donation in time.
很多重症或急需的病人
Many status one, or most in-need patients
并不能及时得到救命的移植
do not receive a transplant in time to save their lives.
田纳西州  你们有77票
Tennessee! You have 77 votes.
你们要投给谁
How do you cast them?
志愿者州...
From the Volunteer State...
田纳西州的别称
总统马上会接听电话
the president will be with you in a moment.
在美国副总统提名投票上  将73票
...we cast 73 votes for vice president
投给凯瑟琳·杜兰特国务卿
to Secretary Catherine Durant,
4票投给约瑟夫·贝克参议员
and four votes to Senator Joseph Baker.
-凯茜  -跟恩莱特的见面很顺利
- Cathy! - The meeting with Enright went well.
我之后给他打了电话  他说被你折服了
I put a call into him afterwards. He said you charmed him.
-我们有多少票了  -949
- That puts us where? - Nine-forty-nine.
这轮投票还赢不了  但也拉近了差距
We won't make this ballot, but we're getting close.
下轮肯定行  我确定
Next one. I'm sure of it.
等我们拿到最终数字再谈吧
Let's talk once we get the final numbers.
好的  再见
Will do. Bye.
德克萨斯州  你们有237票
Texas, you have 237 votes.
我今晚要打的电话名单呢
Do you have my call list for tonight?
你们要投给谁
How do you cast them?
秘书长女士  我是鲁伊斯·特雷霍
Madam Secretary, my name is Ruiz Trejo.
好的  我在电梯里遇见乔瓦尼了
I see. Uh, I ran into Giovanni in the elevator.
你可以划掉他
You can cross him off.
再划掉米尔福德
And cross off Milford.
她说她到死都只会支持贝克
She said she's gonna back Baker till the bitter end.
我们把所有票都投给了我们本区人
We cast all of our votes to our native daughter,
第一夫人
the First Lady,
也是美国未来的副总统
and the future Vice President of the United States of America,
克莱尔·安德伍德
Claire Underwood.
谢谢  德州  谢...
Thank you, Texas. And thank...
全部237票吗  太好了
All 237? Nice.
我母亲狠狠敲打了犹豫不定的
My mother brought the hammer down on the holdouts.
我刚发了奥斯丁和休斯顿的捐赠者名单给你
I just emailed you my donor lists for Austin and Houston.
应该至少能拿到两百万
Should be at least two million in the bank.
-琼斯女士  -太好了
- Ms. Jones. - Oh, that's great.
我得挂了  记者来了
Oh, I gotta go. The cameras are here.
琼斯女士  整个州都投给第一夫人
Ms. Jones, the entire state for the First Lady.
您如何评价呢
Will you comment?
我认为我们一致的选票就是你想要的评论
I think our unanimous vote is all the commentary you need.
总统在国情咨文中
Now, the president endorsed your race, uh,
背书了您竞选接替您母亲
your mother's vacant seat, uh, during the State of the Union.
是的  作为领跑者我很骄傲
He sure did, and I'm proud to be the front-runner.
这背书会不会跟您
Did that endorsement have anything to do
对第一夫人的支持有关呢
with your support of the First Lady?
我不否认安德伍德夫妇对我很好
Look, I won't deny that the Underwoods have been good to me.
但不是的  他们叫我投给凯瑟琳·杜兰特
But no. They asked me to vote for Catherine Durant. And
虽然我认为杜兰特国务卿
while I think Secretary Durant
会是这项工作的好人选
would be a wonderful woman for the job,
但我觉得克莱尔是最好的人选
I think Claire is the best woman for the job.
我真的很感激  戴安
Well, I really appreciate it, Diane,
我知道凯茜也会很感激的
and I know Cathy will as well.
好吧  再联络
All right, we'll speak soon.
新草稿
New draft.
莉安让我再改改一些用词...
LeAnn wanted me to work in some phrases...
和一些关键强调词
and keyword amplifiers.
我只求你打个电话
All I'm asking is that you make the call.
如果是你说  他会听的
He'll listen if it comes from you.
好生硬
It seems very clunky.
我同意
I agree.
能不能...
Is there a way to...
写出她想要的但写得...
put in what she wants and make it...
-更优雅一点  -他还在为
- more elegant? - He's still pissed about
我担任党鞭时否决的没用国防法案生气
that limp-dick defense bill I killed when I was whip...
也许吧...但我有我的限制
Maybe... but I have my limitations.
我觉得你不太相信她的分析
Well, you don't have much faith in her analytics, I don't think.
都是用数字在说话
It's paint by numbers.
是啊  她还说
Yes, well, she also says
你一直在疏远其他讲稿撰写人
that you've been alienating some of the other speechwriters.
他们的平庸才是他们被疏远的原因
Eh, well, their mediocrity is what's alienating them.
我对那个过敏
I'm allergic to it.
-我独自工作更好  -让我跟布赖斯谈谈
- I work better alone. - Let me speak to Bryce
看看我能做点什么
and then see what I can do.
没错  让韦斯特电子来做
That's right. WestCAM should do it.
最好是今晚
Well, tonight if you can.
实在不行就早上...
The morning is fine if you can't...
我得走了  晚点再讨论讲稿吧
I have to go. Let's discuss the speech later.
对  我只需要你们州再来三票
Yeah, all I need is just three more from your state
我们就赢了
and we've got it.
对  就再多几票
Yes, just a... just a few more.
三票
Like, three.
对  我也是  我们明天再聊
Yes, and so do I. I'll talk to you tomorrow.
晚安
Good night.
汤姆
Tom.
你来之后  我们都没时间
I feel like we haven't even had a chance to say hello
打个招呼
since you came on board.
你是个大忙人
You're a busy man.
我从来没闲下来过
I don't know the opposite.
也有好处  比如睡眠
It has its upsides. Like sleep.
还有朋友
And friends.
那个怎么样了
How's the, uh...
要不是得吃药
You know, if it weren't for the pills,
我一整天都不会想到这事
I could go through entire days without even thinking about it.
不知道那孩子如果知道
I wonder what that kid would think...
他成了总统身体的一部分会怎么想
if he knew that part of him was inside of the president's body.
真悲剧啊
Tragic, huh?
但话又说回来
But, then again,
一个人的悲剧是另一个人的宝藏
one man's tragedy is another man's treasure,
-是不是  -垃圾
- isn't that right? - Trash.
什么
What?
"一个人的垃圾"  应该这么说
"One man's trash." That's how the saying goes.
对了
Oh, right.
讲稿怎么样了
How's the speech coming?
这是你提名演讲的先导讲话  但...
Well, this is for the introduction to your acceptance speech, but...
不该是她自己的提名演讲吗
shouldn't it be for her own acceptance?
你想让克莱尔赢  而不是杜兰特
You want Claire to win, not Durant.
第一夫人当...
A First Lady as the...
真荒唐
That's ludicrous.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
而且我觉得你也不
And I don't think you do either.
也许我错了
Maybe I'm wrong.
但如果我说得对
But if I'm right...
她会需要一份终结者性的讲稿
she's gonna need the speech to end all speeches.
提前让我有准备会比较好
And it would be good for me to know that.
我还有其他事
I have some more work to do.
州长  你好吗
Governor! How are you?
对  我也希望我在俄勒冈州
Yeah, well, I wish I was in Oregon, too,
但我现在在亚特兰大
but I'm here in Atlanta
这里比站街女的屄还湿热
where it's muggier than a street hooker's twat.
能和国务卿杜兰特以及
I am honored to be mentioned
贝克参议员相提并论  我倍感荣幸
with Secretary Durant and Senator Baker.
他们都是经验丰富的政治家
They're seasoned politicians.
但我已经有工作了
But I already have a job,
美国的第一夫人
First Lady of the United States.
德州的选票占比超过5%
Well, Texas is over 5% of the vote.
也是我的家乡  所以别想得太多了
And my home state, so let's not make more of it than it is.
克莱尔
Claire!
祝贺你  你现在已经是第五名了
Congratulations. I think you're in fifth place now.
对  而你是当之无愧的第一
Yeah, with you in first, where you should be.
杜兰特国务卿  您认为第一夫人有机会吗
Secretary Durant, do you think the First Lady has a shot?
我觉得德州给了她一次机会
I think Texas just gave her one.
不开玩笑
Kidding aside, do you think
您认为她有外交经验吗
she has the foreign policy experience?
这无关紧要  就像我今早说的
It's beside the point. And like I said this morning,
我鼓励所有人  也包括德州人
I encourage everyone, including Texas,
给杜兰特国务卿投票
to vote for Secretary Durant.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood--
失陪一下
You know what, if you'll excuse me,
我想继续去打电话
I want to get back to the phones,
确保凯茜得到提名
make sure Cathy gets this nomination.
-谢谢  -能单独说句话吗
- Thank you. - May I have a moment?
当然
Oh, of course.
有没有人问过你勃兰登堡的事
Did anyone ask you about Brandenburg
或者问过你的手下  打探你在其中的角色
or any of your people and your involvement there?
勃兰登堡
Brandenburg?
没有  我们不是都解决了
No, we put that to bed.
我之前也这么以为
That's what I thought,
所以亚当·古尔德告诉我
which is why I was surprised when Adam Gould told me
知情人说功劳全是你的时  我很惊讶
that he had sources saying you deserved all the credit.
我们都统一了说法
We all agreed to what our version of the story is,
这么说有人不听话了
so somebody isn't toeing the line.
肯定不是白宫的工作人员
Well, I'm sure it's not White House staff.
他肯定只是在瞎猜  想挑拨对立
I bet he's just fishing, trying to start some rivalry.
那样就好了  如果他问你或者其他人
Well, I'd be grateful, if he asks you, or anyone else--
当然  而且我一直坚持我们的说法
Of course. And I've been sticking to our story...
是你让俄罗斯人做出让步
which it was you that got the Russians to back down,
我到那儿只是去支持你
and I was just there to support you.
代表们如果知道不会满意的
That wouldn't look good to the delegates,
是你单独和佩特罗夫见了面
the fact that you met with Petrov without me.
会看上去像我根本没控制住...
It would look like I wasn't in command of--
我们讨论的内容不需要让人知道
No one needs to know what we discussed.
你没什么可担心的  凯茜  真的
You have nothing to worry about, Cathy. Honestly.
对  我可以帮你接通
Well, yeah. I can get you on the phone
农业部长的电话
with the Secretary of Agriculture,
但如果你想抗旱救灾
but if you want drought relief,
那只有史蒂文斯和洛佩兹可远远不够
I'm gonna need more than just Stevens and Lopez.
贝克那边有什么安排吗
Has anything been set up with Baker yet?
明早在他的房里
Tomorrow morning, in his room.
这卡得也太紧了
Well, that's cutting it close.
他今晚还要和
He's at a big dinner with
佛罗里达国会代表团吃饭
the Florida congressional delegation tonight.
那好  请务必回电
Well, all right, and call me back.
凯茜已经听见风声了
The rumors have gotten to Cathy.
我们本来就是想把风声传出去
Well, we did want them to spread. That was the idea.
我们得有人找她谈谈
I think one of us needs to speak with her.
但计划是要等到万不得已再去
Yeah, but the plan was to wait till it was inevitable.
如果我们不尽快把她拉进来  弗兰西斯
If we don't involve her sooner than later, Francis,
她可能会背叛我们
she could turn on us.
那好  你去见贝克
All right, you take your meeting with Baker.
-我去和凯茜谈  你去安排  -好  先生
- I'll talk to Cathy. You set that up. - Yes, sir.
你打算说到什么地步
How much are you going to say?
让她有心理准备就行
Just enough to prepare her.
不少人来电问安德伍德夫人和俄罗斯的事
A lot of calls about Mrs. Underwood in Russia.
你否认了
Denying?
我无视了  基本上就是等于默认了
Ignoring, which is the same as confirming.
-很好  -克莱尔在里面吗
- Good. - Claire in there?
她正在和总统私谈
She's speaking privately with the president.
我进去她不会介意的
Oh, I'm sure she won't mind.
查莉安查得怎么样了
Where are we with LeAnn?
-她没有问题  -不可能
- She's clean. - No.
我不相信
I refuse to believe that.
道格  如果我们的竞选经理完蛋了
Doug, if our campaign manager bites the dust,
这对我们没有好处
that hurts us.
这是我给你的任务
I gave you a task.
我继续查
And I'll keep at it.
今早捐肝的新闻做得漂亮
Nice coverage on the liver thing this morning.
我给你发了些链接
I emailed you some links.
孩子们都大了  结婚了
Boys are older now, both married.
第三个孙子也要出世了
Got a third grandkid on the way.
如今我们不怎么去湖边了
We don't get out to the lake much these days.
混首都圈代价不小啊
Washington takes its toll.
那是自然
It sure does.
我这些年牺牲了不少  安德伍德夫人
I've made a lot of sacrifices over the years, Mrs. Underwood.
最主要的就是没时间陪孩子
Time with my boys, that's a big one.
我不知道能不能赢  但我参与进来了
Who knows if I'll win, but I'm in the mix.
我不能牺牲这次机会
And I can't sacrifice this opportunity
为凯茜·杜兰特铺路
to pave the way for Cathy Durant.
你赢不了的  参议员  你我都清楚
You won't win, Senator. We both know that.
可我不能帮她
But I can't help her.
我知道你们两个有分歧
Now, I realize you two don't get along.
她看不惯我
She despises me.
老实说  我对她也是一样
And I have to say, the feeling is mutual.
-听着  -她一就任国务卿
- Well, listen-- - The moment she became Secretary of State,
就让共和党人
she got the Republicans to
把我从外事委员会赶出来了
remove me from the Foreign Relations Committee.
弗兰西斯对此很不高兴
And Francis was very upset about that.
可这都是过去的事了
But that was the past.
我们还是放眼未来吧
Let's talk about the future.
党内对克莱尔如此支持  我们都没想到
This support for Claire, it's caught us both off guard.
但我要你来做副总统
But you are my choice for vice president.
这一点不会变
Nothing has changed on that front.
我只是担心那些传言
Well, my only concern are the rumors.
的确会威胁我的胜算
They could damage my chances.
对  我们会想办法应对的
Yes. And we'll do what we can to combat those.
克莱尔也是这么说的  我很感激
That's what Claire said, too, and it's much appreciated.
但是如果  仅仅是如果
But, if, and-- Oh, God, it's a big if.
但是如果
But what if...
对克莱尔的支持成了气候
support for Claire picks up steam...
你不是真以为有这可能吧
Well, you don't actually think that will happen?
当然不了  第一夫人哪能当副总统
Oh, no. I mean, a First Lady as VP?
怎么行
No.
党内想要个有经验的人  人民也是
The party wants someone with experience, and so does the country.
那是当然
Absolutely.
但这次是开放党代会
But... it is an open convention,
所以我们必须
and so we have to operate
准备应对一切可能发生的情况
with the belief that anything could happen.
媒体是对这个想法十分感兴趣
I mean, the press is certainly enjoying imagining it.
那可不  这种头条吸引眼球
Well, sure. It makes for a good story.
而这种新闻我们也没办法控制
Yeah, and it's the kind of coverage that we can't really control.
我是说
You know, I mean,
这种风声会自己落地生根
these things have a way of taking on a life of their own.
就像佐伊·巴恩斯的报道
Like the Zoe Barnes story
影响了我担任国务卿的提名
did about my nomination for Secretary of State.
只不过那是我们设计好的
Except that one we planted.
-这次你没有吗  -当然没有
- And this one you didn't. - No, absolutely not!
克莱尔都不知道怎么回应这些支持票
I mean, Claire was mortified by those votes.
你是说  如果新闻报道影响了足够多的人
What you're saying is if the coverage influences enough people...
我们必须有所准备
Well, we have to be prepared for that.
当然了
I mean...
从政治角度讲  这简直是灾难
of course, politically, it would be a disaster.
也许是  也许不是
Maybe, maybe not.
你觉得不一定吗
You don't think so?
我个人觉得克莱尔会非常称职
Well, personally, I think Claire would do an excellent job.
你这么说我实在是没想到
Well, I am very surprised to hear you say that.
你不相信她会吗
You don't believe she would?
我只是从来没这么想过
Well, I've just never really considered it.
第一夫人  当副总统
The First Lady? As vice president?
有251个党代表支持这个想法
Well, 251 delegates think it's a good idea.
他们大多来自德州  那只是玩笑
Well, most of those were from Texas, which was a lark.
是吗
Was it?
支持我的党代表不比你少  参议员
I have as many delegates as you do, Senator.
-但如果你开始支持我  -你得票翻倍
- But if you start pushing yours my way... - You double.
并且票数最多
And take the lead.
-然后凯茜再支持你获得提名  -就是这样
- And then Cathy puts you over the top. - That's the idea.
她也支持你吗
So she's in on this?
她会的
She will be.
假设克莱尔真的票数领先
Well, let's say Claire does take the lead,
先不管可能性有多大吧
however unlikely that may be...
-我看基本不可能  -先假设她领先了
- Very unlikely, I would say. - Well, let's say she does.
你打算怎么办
What do you propose?
我还真不知道
I honestly don't know.
你肯定得支持她吧
Well, you'd have to support her, wouldn't you?
你总不能抛弃自己的妻子
You can't abandon your own wife.
那倒是  可我也不能抛弃你啊
Uh, true, but I can't abandon you either.
如果她真的领先了
Well, if she took the lead,
我想我也得支持她了
I suppose I'd have to support her, too.
我决不会要求你做那样的事
No, I would never ask you to do that.
你不必要求我  我们是一边的
But you don't have to ask. We're on the same team here.
那我就直接问了
Well, to be perfectly blunt...
我有什么好处
what's in it for me?
你想要什么好处
What would it take?
来推销的是你  你说说吧
You're doing the selling. Make me an offer.
假设克莱尔成功了
Let's say Claire gets it.
如果你赢了的话  我可以留任吧
I assume I stay on, if you get the general.
那肯定
Oh, absolutely.
我可不敢想像
I cannot imagine the next
接下来的四年里没有你来当美国的...
four years without you being my Secretary of...
国务卿
...State.
你要把凯茜的工作给我
You'd give me Cathy's job?
我们是这么打算的
We're prepared to.
-道格  -国务卿女士
- Doug. - Madam Secretary.
出了个问题  先生
We have an issue, sir.
当我最早警告总统哈里发国会不断壮大
When I first warned the president that ICO would grow,
并迅速扩张时  他什么都没做
and grow quickly, he did nothing.
昨天哈里发国的领袖发了这条推特
Yesterday, the leaders of ICO sent out this tweet.
"苏瓦尔已被我们夺下
"As Suwar is ours.
幼发拉底河将被鲜血染红"
Soon heads will roll into the Euphrates."
不仅用阿拉伯文发  还有英语
That wasn't just in Arabic, that was in English,
以及其他16种语言
and sent out in 16 other languages.
他们善于媒体攻势  在全球范围内招募人手
They're media savvy, they're recruiting around the globe.
他们现在资金和人手都很充足
They have the money and the manpower now.
一旦他们进入幼发拉底河流域
Once they get to the Euphrates,
他们将扼住北叙利亚的命门
they'll have a choke hold on northern Syria.
我们必须采取行动  总统先生  马上行动
We must act, Mr. President, and we must act now.
一般来说  党代会有种
Normally, there's a tradition of sportsmanship
传统的竞争精神
when it comes to conventions.
一名候选人保持低调
One candidate lays low
让另一名候选人得到最大关注
so the other gets his or her moment in the spotlight.
但是总统不仅
But not only is the president
在无视一个重大的世界安全威胁
ignoring a great threat to the world's security,
他还侮辱了唯一站出来为我们大声疾呼的人
he's insulted the one man who stood up and spoke out for us all.
这篇详细阐述了
When this profile came out
将军刚刚所说的内容的专访发行后
about everything the general just mentioned,
白宫竟然指责他利用恐怖主义做政治文章
the White House said that he was politicizing terrorism.
而当我宣布布洛哈特将军
And when I announced that General Brockhart
将成为我的竞选搭档后
was going to be my running mate,
总统竞选团队竟称  我原话引用
the president's campaign said, and I quote,
"为将军拿爱国换仕途的行径感到惋惜"
"It's a shame the general traded in patriotism for careerism."
这可实在是称不上竞争精神
Now, I don't call that very sportsmanlike.
这就是下作
I call it disgraceful.
总统为这个国家打过几场仗
How many wars has the president fought for his country?
我们都知道  一次都没有
I think we all know, none.
而他却质疑这位曾多次为国而战的人的爱国心
And he questions the patriotism of a man who has fought in many?
你听好  总统先生
You hear me, Mr. President.
我要求你对哈里发国采取措施
I demand that you do something about ICO.
我要求你对将军道歉
And I demand that you make an apology to the general.
你不做到这两点  我们就不离开亚特兰大
And we're not leaving Atlanta until you've done both.
各大电视台都在直播
Live on every network right now.
他这步棋我服气
I gotta hand it to him.
不知道是不是他自己的主意
I wonder if this was his idea,
因为都有点我的风格了
'cause it's almost something like I would do.
不管他  外面35度呢  让他熬下去吧
We ignore him. It's 95 degrees. Let him sweat it out.
我们越是不理他  他得到的关注就会越高
I think the longer we ignore him, the more attention they'll get.
我同意莉安
I agree with LeAnn.
那就道歉吧
So apologize.
无非是面子而已
It's only pride.
如果您同意  我可以来道歉  先生
I can do it if you want, sir.
是我写的声明
I wrote the statement.
不  只有弗兰西斯亲自出面才管用
No, it only works if it comes from Francis.
克莱尔说得对
Claire's right.
除了道歉  我们还可以做更多
And we can do more than just apologize.
我可以和这混蛋见面
I can meet with the bastard.
州长和将军指出的问题都非常重要
The issues the governor and the general raise are important ones.
这超越两党分歧  甚至超越政治
They transcend party affiliations and, quite frankly, politics.
鉴于此  我在此邀请州长
And so in that spirit, I'm inviting the governor
来这里和我见面
to come here and join me,
这样我们可以举行闭门会谈  因为
so that we can have a conversation privately because...
无论最终谁当选  都要对付哈里发国
whoever becomes the president is going to have to deal with ICO
以及我们在世界各地面临的其他恐怖威胁
and all of the other terrorist threats that we face around the globe.
所以我期待听到
So I'm looking forward to hearing
他们可能有的任何想法和方案
whatever ideas and solutions that they may have...
因为聪明的总统会偷任何人的好主意
because a smart president will steal good ideas from anyone.
我们用仁慈干掉他们吧
Let's kill them with kindness, shall we?
-州长  -总统先生
- Governor. - Mr. President.
请让将军接一下电话好吗
Would you please put the General on the line?
先生
Sir?
将军
General...
你对这个国家的贡献深受看重
your service to this country is greatly valued
你的爱国精神也是不容置疑的
and your patriotism is without doubt.
在激烈的竞选之中  我们过火了
And in the heat of the campaign, well, we went too far.
我们发表了不该发表的声明
We issued statements that we shouldn't have,
为此我要向你道歉
and for that I want to apologize,
希望你能接受
and I do hope that you will accept it.
对我而言  除掉哈里发国
Far more important to me than an apology
远比道歉重要  总统先生
is eliminating ICO, Mr. President.
我非常赞同  将军
I couldn't agree with your more, General.
麻烦你把电话交回给州长
If you'd be so kind as to put the Governor back on the phone.
我收到你的邀请了  总统先生
I received your invitation, Mr. President.
那你会来吗  州长
And will you join us, Governor?
得是为了行动  而不是空谈才行
Only if it leads to real action, not just talk.
我向你保证  州长
I can promise you, Governor,
也向整个美国保证  不会是空谈
and the rest of America that it will not just be talk.
那好  如果真有助于保卫自由的话
Then, yes. If it truly leads to securing our freedom.
非常感谢  我期待与你见面
Thank you very much. I look forward to seeing you.
感谢大家
Thank you all very much.
这边请  州长
Right this way, Governor.
你觉得这样好吗
Do you think this a good idea?
我还有什么选择  他接我的招了
What choice do I have? He called my bluff.
欢迎  州长
Welcome, Governor.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
我安排了一个房间
I have a room set up for us.
来
Here.
吃些午餐
Have some lunch.
我们有火腿  还有些火鸡
We've got ham, and I think some turkey.
不用了  谢谢
I'm good, but thanks.
真的吗
Really?
看你演的那一出  我以为你喜欢火腿[演过头]呢
After the stunt you just pulled, I would've thought you love ham.
你特意放在这里的
You put this here on purpose.
一点读物
Well, a little reading material, you know.
作为消遣
Something to pass the time.
我刚收到本·格兰特的短信
I just got a text from Ben Grant
说我们来这里后
saying searches for this issue is
对这一期的搜索量爆表
going through the roof since we showed up here.
本·格兰特是波利跳的老板
Ben Grant owns Pollyhop...
没错
That's right.
而他又是你的人
And you own Ben Grant.
这不就是权力吗  你能揽到的人
Isn't that what power is? The people you collect?
你那网络直播真是害惨我了
You really screwed me with that webcast.
我本来把一切都安排好了
I had everything all planned out.
联邦选举委员会  司法部
The Federal Election Commission, the Department of Justice.
我就等着看你灰飞烟灭呢
I was looking forward to watching you go down in flames...
甚至锒铛入狱
maybe even behind bars.
抱歉让你扫兴了
Well, I'm sorry I ruined your fun.
不过挺难堪的  不是吗
It's a bit embarrassing, though, isn't it?
把你们最亲密的镜头公之于众
I mean, sharing all your most intimate moments?
你孩子们的影像
Videos of your children?
我为我的家庭骄傲  怎么会难堪呢
I'm proud of my family. Why would I be embarrassed?
为了赢得所有人的喜爱  要屈尊至此
Well, just that you have to stoop so low to win everyone's love.
看起来挺绝望的  不是吗
It feels a bit desperate, doesn't it?
你在所有民调中都落后15个百分点
You're 15 points behind in every poll.
绝望的人应该是你
So, if anyone's desperate, it should be you.
做总统的关键
Well, the key to being President
不只在于赢得胜利
is not only winning your battles,
而是要赢得有尊严
it's winning them with dignity.
我们谈不谈哈里发国了
Should we talk about ICO?
老天  我们为什么要谈那个呢
Oh, God. Why would we want to do that?
这是我们会面的原因
It's why we're meeting.
对了
Oh, right.
"真正的谈话  真正的行动"
"Real talk, real action."
那就是你关注的  是吗
That's what you're all about, isn't it?
如果你想谈  我们可以谈  不过
Well, I suppose we could if you want to, but...
我们也可以把这一切暂时放下
then again we could just take a break from it all
放松一下
and relax a bit.
老天
God.
这火鸡一股橡胶味
This turkey tastes like rubber.
总比真的吃橡胶[安全套]要好
Well, it's better than eating a real one.
我被民主党人吹箫时
Oh, I always wear protection
总是要做好保护措施
when I'm getting my dick sucked by the Democrats.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事  没事
I'm fine. I'm fine.
我吃东西时别和我开玩笑  我差点噎死
Don't make me laugh when I'm eating. I nearly choked to death.
那倒是让我当上总统的一个办法
Well, that is one way for me to become president.
-给  -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
-你还好吧  -嗯
- You okay? - Oh, yeah.
你介意我脱掉吗
Do you mind if I take these off?
是崭新的鞋  还没磨合好呢
They're brand new and I'm still breaking 'em in.
你喜欢玩电子游戏  对吧
You like to play video games, right?
你从哪听说的
Now, how did you hear about that?
汤姆·耶茨
Tom Yates.
对了
Oh, yes.
汤姆·耶茨
Tom Yates.
这个人你没能揽到  是不是
That's one person you weren't able to collect, were you?
你是怎么把他招回来的
What did you do to get him back?
他肯定动过心的
Oh, look, I'm sure he was tempted.
毕竟他是个写小说的
He is a fiction writer, after all.
而你是个纽约的共和党人
You're a New York Republican.
这种虚构剧情很诱人啊  是吧
That's an attractive fiction, isn't it?
你是个来自南卡罗莱纳的民主党
And you're a Democrat from South Carolina,
这更像虚构的情节
that's even bigger fiction.
你说对了
Well, there you go.
而且我是个纽约的共和党  基本上就是民主党
And I'm a New York Republican, which is basically a Democrat.
如果你是民主党人  那没有人可以阻挡你
If you were a Democrat, you'd be unstoppable.
你绝对是新一代肯尼迪
You'd be the new JFK.
如果你是共和党  那你会是谁  尼克松吗
And if you were a Republican, who'd you be? Nixon?
尼克松可是个高效得多的总统
Nixon was a far more effective president.
人们崇拜肯尼迪只是因为他被爆头了
The only reason people glorify Kennedy is because he got shot.
你不是也挨了一枪吗
Well, you've got that going for you, too, now, don't you?
而你有你的搜索引擎
And you've got your search engine
和你的家庭视频
and all your little home videos.
如果人们想了解你
See, if people want a piece of you...
你就满足他们  对不对
you give it to them, right?
这就是人们想要的吗
Oh, is that what people want?
了解你
A piece of you?
你玩电子游戏吗
Do you play video games?
不  但我孩子玩
No. My kids do.
我儿子查理特别爱玩一个游戏
There's this one game that my son Charlie, he loves to play.
名字叫"细胞吞噬"
It's called Agar.Io.
我得承认我自己时不时也玩一玩
I have to admit, I might have played it a couple of times myself.
你一开始只是一个小点
You start out as a little dot.
然后你四处移动
And then you go around
吞噬其他的点  你就会变大
eating these other dots and you get bigger.
你变得越大
And the bigger you get,
就越得小心别被其他玩家更大的点吃掉
you gotta avoid getting eaten by the bigger players.
与此同时你还要继续吞噬比你小的点
Meanwhile, you're trying to eat the smaller players.
听着挺像总统竞选的
Sounds a little like running for president.
那么现在和你对战的都是真人吗
So, are you playing with real people right now?
没错  来自全世界的玩家
Yeah. From all over the world.
来  你试试
Here, you try it.
-呀  我被吞了  -按这个键
- Oh, I got eaten. - Press that.
我明白了  我又变小了
Ah, oh, I see. It makes you small again.
对  你每次都得重头开始
Yeah, you gotta start over from square one every single time.
我的天  我又被吞了
Oh, God. I got eaten again.
如果其他玩家知道对手是什么人
I wonder what the other players would think
不知道会怎么想
if they knew who they were playing against.
我倒挺喜欢匿名的
Oh, I'm rather enjoying the anonymity.
这真是史无前例
This is unprecedented.
总统和康威州长
The president and Governor Conway
正在大会会场举行闭门会谈
are meeting right now at the convention hall.
两名候选人面对面
Two candidates, face to face.
他们已经进去十分钟了
They've been in there for about ten minutes,
据说在讨论如何应对哈里发国问题
supposedly discussing the ICO situation.
而两名总统候选人继续进行
Now, while the private meeting between the two candidates
闭门会谈的同时
continues behind closed doors,
场内代表们正在
delegates on the floor
准备进行下一轮投票
are gearing up for the next round of voting for...
我们得下去了  下一轮投票马上就要开始了
We should head down. The next ballot is starting soon.
-我马上就去  -在第二轮投票中
- I'll be down in a minute. - In the second round of voting
四分之一的代表改变了选择
a quarter of the delegates changed their votes,
支持第一夫人安德伍德的呼声越来越高
support for First Lady Claire Underwood is picking up steam,
这要部分归功于今天的头条新闻
thanks in part to today's breaking story
称安德伍德夫人在勃兰登堡会谈中立下大功
about Mrs. Underwood's involvement in the Brandenburg negotiations.
参议员斯考特·希尔投下的一张支持票
A single vote from Senator Scott Sheer
扩展到整个德州代表团转而支持第一夫人
expanded to support from the entire Texas delegation.
你好像  有个电话
You've, uh, got a call.
我最好接下  肯定是大事  他们才会打给我
Yeah, I better take that. They only call if it's important.
我是威尔
Yeah, this is Will.
好  转接过来吧
Yes, put it through.
-失陪  -没事
- Um, excuse me. - Sure.
说吧
Go ahead.
可恶  什么都听不到
Damn! Nothing.
这是战争迷雾
The fog of war.
密室里的密室
A back room within a back room.
不管他在里面搞什么阴谋
Whatever's being plotted in there,
肯定对我不利
I can tell you it's no good for me.
每到这种时候我都巴不得是尼克松
You know, it's at times like these I wish I was Nixon,
严密监听着每一个角落
had every nook and cranny bugged.
-总统先生  -你那个同事
- Mr. President? - Your colleague.
他的定向性有多高
How targeted can he get?
我们实在不该在电话里讨论这些事
We really shouldn't be discussing this over the phone.
他能单独针对一个人吗
Can he isolate a specific person?
技术上讲可以  但是
Technically, yes, but--
一段特定的对话呢
A conversation?
程序中有专门防止这么做的闭锁机制
There are catch mechanisms in the program to prevent that.
他可以进行破解  但会留下痕迹
He can override, but it leaves a trail.
他还在研究如何掩盖痕迹
He's still figuring out how to mask it.
我们纽约来的朋友
Our friend from New York.
我想知道他现在正在说什么
I want to know what he's saying right now.
先生  我表示强烈反对
Sir, I strongly advise against that.
我也建议我们挂电话
I also advise that we hang up.
好吧  我挂了
All right, I'm hanging up.
州长  我们该出去了吧
Governor, should we head out?
马上  总统先生
Just a moment, Mr. President.
目前对于亚特兰大有很大期待...
There's a great deal of anticipation in Atlanta...
谁打来的
Who was that?
总统  他想知道最新的代表投票数
The president. He just wanted the latest delegate count.
...下一轮投票还有几分钟就开始了
...and we're minutes away from the next ballot.
这是昨天上一轮投票的图表
Here's a graphic of the last round yesterday.
国务卿凯瑟琳·杜兰特
Secretary Catherine Durant
以22%的代表票数领先
led the way with 22% of delegates.
道格很不高兴
Doug hates it.
他不高兴什么
He hates what?
你可以直接接触总统
That you have direct access to the president
不用通过他
without going through him.
他希望你走人
He wants you gone.
道格这么跟你说的
Doug told you that?
他要我找你的把柄
He wants me to dig something up on you.
我还没找到
I haven't found anything yet.
你不会找到的  因为我没有把柄
And you won't, because there isn't anything.
我知道  否则我现在已经找到了
I know. Otherwise, I would've found it by now.
你为什么要跟我说这个
Why are you telling me this?
因为如果不是你走  我做不到  我就得走
Because either you're gone or I am, if I don't deliver.
除非你给我点什么
Unless you give me something.
第一夫人克莱尔·安德伍德
...First Lady Claire Underwood,
惊人地出现在第五位
a surprising fifth place show...
可以是个小把柄  没什么大危害的
It can be small. Nothing too damaging.
只要让我有东西给他看
Just so I have something to show him.
在我报道总统选举的三十年职业生涯中
In my 30 years of covering presidential politics,
从未见过这样的事
I've never seen anything like it.
不好意思
Sorry about that.
没关系
That's all right.
我们出去吧  下轮投票马上要开始了
Shall we go out? The next ballot is about to start.
你想一起看吗
You want to watch it together?
我们在这里待得越久  看起来越好
It might look better, the longer we're in here.
就像我们为美国的未来搏斗了一番似的
Like we grappled with the future of America.
除非你想出去跟群众在一起
Unless you'd rather be out there with the masses.
天呐  群众们
Oh, Christ. The masses.
-我也是这么觉得  -我们现在开始
- I feel the same way. - We will now commence
为我们党
the third ballot
副总统候选人提名进行第三轮投票
for the nomination of our party's vice presidential candidate.
我们从阿拉巴马州开始
We will start with Alabama.
秘书长女士
Madam Secretary,
伟大的阿拉巴马州
the great state of Alabama,
在美国副总统提名投票上
for Vice President of the United States,
将29票投给国务卿凯瑟琳·杜兰特
casts 29 votes for Secretary Catherine Durant,
26票投给第一夫人克莱尔·安德伍德
26 votes for the First Lady Claire Underwood,
剩下的三票投给莫比尔市长
and our three remaining votes for the Mayor of Mobile,
阿拉巴马州的简·温斯洛普
Alabama's own Jane Winthrop.
红潮[阿拉巴马球队]威猛
Roll Tide!
阿拉斯加州  接下来是你们
Alaska, you're next.
八票投给国务卿杜兰特
Eight votes for Secretary of State Durant,
六票投给约瑟夫·贝克参议员
six votes for Senator Joseph Baker,
四票投给第一夫人克莱尔·安德伍德
four votes for First Lady Claire Underwood.
加利福尼亚州
California,
你们有476票
you have 476 votes.
233票投给凯瑟琳·杜兰特
Two hundred and thirty-three for Catherine Durant,
152票投给约瑟夫·贝克
152 for Joseph Baker,
91票投给克莱尔·安德伍德
91 for Claire Underwood.
那对第一夫人是极大的支持
That's huge for the First Lady.
让她上升到第三位  并逼近第二位
That puts her in third, and she's closing in on second.
特拉华州
Delaware.
12票给杜兰特
Twelve for Durant,
11票给克莱尔·安德伍德
11 for Claire Underwood,
4票给贝克
four for Baker.
夏威夷州  接下来是你们
Hawaii, you're next.
17票投给第一夫人
Seventeen for the First Lady,
14票投给国务卿凯瑟琳·杜兰特
and 14 for Secretary of State Catherine Durant.
她真的有机会
She's got a real shot.
难以置信
Unbelievable!
也没有那么难以置信
Well, not so unbelievable.
44票投给凯瑟琳·杜兰特
Forty-four votes for Catherine Durant,
35票投给克莱尔·安德伍德
35 votes for Claire Underwood.
路易斯安那州
Louisiana,
你们有61票
you have 61 votes.
你们怎么投
How do you cast them?
秘书长女士
Madam Secretary...
路易斯安那州把61票投给国务卿凯瑟琳·杜兰特
Louisiana casts its 61 votes for President of the United States
竞选美国总统
to Secretary of State Catherine Durant.
路易斯安那州  你想说的是副总统吧
Louisiana, I assume you mean vice president.
我说的就是总统
I mean president.
秘书长女士  路易斯安那州
Madam Secretary, the state of Louisiana
认为这次大会应该向
believes this convention should be open
所有位置开放  包括总统
for all parts of the ticket, including president.
路易斯安那州
Louisiana!
正如大会昨天上午达成的共识
As the convention agreed to yesterday morning,
我们会先选出副总统候选人
we are taking vice presidential nominations first,
以在整个大会上进行那一程序
in order for that process to take place over the full convention.
我们只有一位总统候选人
We have one candidate for president.
任何关于该项投票的讨论
Any further discussion on that balloting
将放在副总统提名程序
will be taken up after the vice presidential nomination process
完成之后
is complete.
如果你不把票投出去的话  视为弃权
If you do not cast your votes, you will forfeit them.
秘书长女士  我们路易斯安那州
Madam Secretary, we, Louisiana,
把副总统提名的61票
cast our 61 votes for vice president,
还是投给凯瑟琳·杜兰特
also for Catherine Durant.
路易斯安那州
Louisiana.
我在他手下干  是他的内阁成员
I work for the man. I'm on his cabinet.
如果总统提名公开竞选  你会同他竞争吗
Would you run against him if his nomination were in play?
我的目标是和总统一起参选  而非互相竞争
My goal is to run with the president, not against him.
听着  我爱我的家乡  路易斯安那
Look, I love my home state of Louisiana,
-但他们太热情  -她会胜任的
- but they're a live bunch... - She'd do a good job.
不过她做国务卿会更出色
She's a much better Secretary of State, though.
我相信事情最终会得到解决的
I'm confident this will all work itself out.
我考虑过你败选之后保留她的位置
I've considered keeping her on after you lose.
你有没有就他们的倒戈与安德伍德总统沟通过
Have you spoken to President Underwood about their defection?
还没有  但我想我很快就会与他谈话的
Not yet, but I'll be speaking with him shortly, I imagine.
不过大会的意义...
Hey, this is part of what a...
-你那通电话  -就在于此
- Your call.  - ...convention is all about.
我也想能居功  但是她找的我
I wish I could take credit, but... but she called me.
不过说回来  当机会到来的时候
Then again, when opportunity strikes...
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
这绝对不算赢得有尊严
Definitely not the way to win with dignity.
杜兰特就她的家乡路易斯安那发表评论
...Durant commenting on her home state of Louisiana.
如果你能赢的话
If you win at all.
我们该出去了
We should get back out there.
你还得争取提名呢
You've got a nomination to fight for.
总统和我的谈话非常顺利
The president and I, we had a great talk.
我们甚至还一起观看了投票
We, uh, even watched the vote together.
但是我想你们肯定更想听他怎么说
But I'm sure you'd rather hear from him on that than me.
谢谢  州长
Well, thank you, Governor.
今天还真是充满意外  不是吗
Today has certainly been full of surprises, hasn't it?
但是话说回来
But, then again,
毕竟休伊·朗就来自路易斯安那州
Louisiana is the state that gave us Huey Long after all.
该州前州长
政绩出色  竞选总统时遇刺
虽然我很想讨论这个话题
As much as I would like to discuss this,
但是我必须着手开始处理
I have to get on with the business
州长和我刚刚探讨的那些问题
that the governor and I have just discussed,
因为当总统比竞选总统重要得多
because the business of the presidency trumps running for it.
-谢谢  州长  -谢谢  总统先生
- Thank you, Governor.  - Thank you, Mr. President.
非常感谢各位
Thank you all very much.
我很愿意回答
I'm happy to answer...
马上把凯茜叫到我房间
I want Cathy in my room, now.
我已经给她打过电话了  她拒绝会面
I already called her. She refuses to meet.
-她什么  -她就是这么说的
- She what?  - That's what she said,
然后她就把电话挂了
and then she hung up.
她的手下也不回我电话
Her staff won't return my calls either.
这事想办成  你必须回华盛顿去
For this to work, you have to go back to Washington.
我不能抛下你一个人处理这件事
I can't leave while you're dealing with this.
如果你留下的话  大家会觉得你在从中渔利
If you stay, it will look like you're taking advantage
并且真的在参选
and campaigning for it.
而这件事的关键就在于让人觉得你没这意思
And the key is to make it look like you're not.
我会找凯茜谈的
I'll speak with Cathy.
不用  我已经在处理了
No, look, I've got that covered.
问题是我们怎么解释你的离开
Question is, how we justify your going.
不去华盛顿
It's not Washington.
应该去德州
It should be Texas.
-你母亲  -上次就好使
- Your mother.  - It worked before.
我明天一早就走
I'll leave first thing in the morning.
带上汤姆一起
Take Tom with you.
-汤姆  -他已经知道了
- Tom?  - Oh, he already knows.
-你告诉他了吗  -他自己猜出来了
- Did you tell him?  - He put it together.
他说  如果你能赢下来的话
He said, if you win this thing...
你必须做一次空前绝后的讲话  他说得对
you have to give the speech of a lifetime, and he's right.
不管你在大会堂里说什么
Whatever you say in that convention hall
都会给我们把你推向全国
will lay the groundwork for how we sell this
打下基础
to the rest of the country.
而这就是我们叫他回来的原因  对吧
And that is why we brought him back, right?
你能坐着就睡着吗
You can sleep like that? Sitting up?
我在哪都能睡着
I can sleep anywhere.
真挺有福的
I'm lucky like that.
我们有活儿要干
We have work to do.
好吧  那就干活儿
All right, let's work.
这段得改
This could be better.
对着我大声读出来
Read it for me. Out loud.
我在婚姻中做我丈夫的搭档已有29年
I've been my husband's partner in marriage for 29 years.
不行
No.
慢点
Slower.
就像你在大会上讲话那样
Like you're going to say it at the convention.
我在婚姻中做我丈夫的搭档已有29年
I've been my husband's partner in marriage for 29 years.
现在  到了我
Now, it's time for me to be..."
这样我能看到你的脸
So I can see your face.
我在婚姻中做我丈夫的搭档已有29年
I've been my husband's partner in marriage for 29 years.
现在到了我在接下来的4年中
Now, it's time for me to be his
进入白宫  继续做他的搭档的时候了
partner in the White House for the next four.
你说得对
You're right.
是得改
We can do better.
美国现有的总统选举  尤其是党内初选制度
是经过漫长的演化才最终形成的
初选选举  选民所选出的并不是总统候选人
而是代表本州参加党代会的代表
所以初选结果计算的并不是候选人获得的选民票数
而是其赢得的州代表数  也就是"选举人票"
这些代表在参加党代会时  再投票决定本党的提名人
19世纪时  各州党内初选结果只是作为一种民意的评测
直到20世纪初  一些州才陆续规定将选举结果同最终的提名挂钩
20世纪60年代之前  民主党  共和党两党挑选提名人时
很大程度上依赖于党代会召开期间
党内大佬和候选人之间的私下谈判和政治交易
1968年  民主党候选人亨福瑞虽然没有赢得任何一个州的初选
但仍靠党代会上的交易成为了民主党提名人
68年后  民主党决定改革初选制度
使各州的初选结果成为决定提名人的主要途径
共和党随后也对党内初选制度做出了相应的改革
无论改革前还是改革后
两党都要求总统候选人必须获得至少过半的选举人票
若多名候选人参选  而没有任何一个获得过半的选举人票
党代会便成为了"开放党代会"
各州代表需要在党代会上进行一轮轮投票
直到某个候选人得到多数票为止
1924年的民主党党代会上
选民代表经过102轮投票才选出最终的提名人
上一次出现需要代表在党代会上
反复投票决定提名人的情况是1952年
正在紧张进行的2016年大选中  共和党阵营群雄争霸
目前虽然地产大亨特朗普在选票上领先
但其他几名候选人仍然十分具有竞争力
而且由于特朗普言行颇受争议
许多共和党内部人士认为  如果不能在选票上打败特朗普
就要寄望于"开放党代会"  通过州代表投票把特朗普选下来